LIZ KOVALCHUK

Web Developer

ABOUT

Trained as a classical musician, I apply inherent understanding of structure, complex pattern recognition and logical symbolism into my code. My experiences as an artist and performer enhance my ability to ensure that my work has a cohesive narrative, great user experience and impeccable attention to detail.

SKILLS & TOOLS

HTML5 Visual Studio CSS/Sass Git & GitHub

JavaScript APIs

PHP Webpack
.NET (MVC) Visual Studio
SQL Firebase
React Laravel

Angular WordPress

EDUCATION

Humber College 2017-18 Post Graduate Certificate Web Development

Ball State University 2012-14 Masters in Music

Roosevelt University 2008-12 Bachevlor of Music

EMPLOYMENT

Simplistics Web Design Full Stack Developer Intern

Summer 2019

Developed igfmining.org using WordPress in team of three. Built assemessment system for upplift.co using gravity forms and custom built WordPress plugins.

Simplistics Web Design Full Stack Developer and Project Manager

September 2018 - February 2019
Maintained code for hangit-up.com
and limor.money. Created custom
WordPress plugin for simplistics.ca to
display google reviews upon contact
form submission. Supervised 8-9
developers and 2 designers while
managing 20-30 projects in queue.

SELECT CONTRACTS

New York Session Symphony Orchestra Contractor and Operations Manager 2016-17

Hired and managed professional musicians. Executed all correspondence for rehearsals, concerts and payments. Identified skill level and character traits of musicians for best fit in team environments.

Networks Touring Production Company

Beauty & the Beast International Tour Principal Cellist 2014-16

CONTACT

lizk.ca 416 254 7530 hello@lizk.ca

